Jimm Hyndrex Inciong

Email: jimminciong163@gmail.com | Mobile: +447415772616

58 Wrottesley Road, London, NW10 5YE

GitHub: https://github.com/Jhiei

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jimm-inciong-5a65b8174/

Profile:

A skilled undergraduate student with great interest in the development of web applications along with 2 years of experience in programming using web technologies such as HTML5, CSS/SCSS, JS and PHP with Laravel. Possesses knowledge of programming in Python and Java. Experienced in creating UI for real-world websites and web applications using Figma.

Technical Skills:

- Full-stack Development (HTML5, CSS3, JS, SCSS, PHP and mySQL)
- Laravel
- Figma
- Python
- Java

Education:

City, University of London 2019 - Present BSc Computer Science

City of Westminster College 2017 – 2019 **D*D*D*** on BTEC Level 3 IT with Extended Diploma

Newman Catholic College 2012 – 2017

- 2 A's including Mathematics and Computer Science
- B on English Language/Literature

Experience:

Fiverr Freelancing – Web Development (January 2020 - Present)

- acquired 5-star rating from all my clients due to satisfaction with the produced web application
- fantastic response time and professional communication maintained throughout whole freelancing career
- designed and developed web projects for clients with their own companies using HTML, CSS, JS and PHP alongside Figma for the wireframes and layout design

BLIX Network – Web Developer Intern (August 2020 – September 2020)

 created web pages for the existing website of BLIX Network using the Laravel framework – from zero experience of Laravel to intermediate

- acquired knowledge of Eloquent during this internship and fetched array of data for the current mentors in the company
- mastery of the MVC model and gained experience with Laravel which is now on intermediate level
- created my own Laravel web application right after this internship
- attended talks, events and webinars hosted by the company itself about inclusive leadership and emotional intelligence

J. P. Morgan – Employability Enhancement Program (April 4, 2019)

- assisted me with important employability skills especially teamwork
- employees of the company were available for questioning about their anecdotes and tips on how to become successful
- learnt how to collaborate in a team and manage my time to become a better employee in the future

Pivotal – Employability Enhancement Program (March 21, 2019 & May 4, 2019)

- planning and creating a program in paper required comprehensive planning and discussion which put teamwork into practice, the project was about how a lift is programmed
- learnt how to create ideas to solve real world problems in a team

Extracurricular Activities:

This individual is a member of the mentoring scheme for new students in the university called CityBuddies in which new students that are not feeling confident about the transition from sixth form/college to university are made to feel welcome and enjoy the university life! Confidence and communication skills upgraded drastically, and many students felt welcome for their new stage in their education.

Interests & Hobbies:

Aside from the interests and profession in web development, I have a deep connection towards music and melodies especially those that are played from guitars. On top of that, sports are a must to have a healthy work-life balance hence volleyball is a must in weekly activities, and I enjoy it very much because it really helps me keep myself healthy. Thus, the work-life stability is perfectly balanced.

Reference:

- Available on Request